<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="buglayout.xml"?>

<!-- The following bugs have been fixed since the omniORB 4.1.6     -->
<!-- release. This file is transformed into html with bugfixes.xsl. -->

<!-- Editors: make sure the content you add is well-formed XML.     -->

<buglist version="4.1.6">

<bug id="7" date="Thu May 23 15:36:56 BST 2013" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>Marshal error sending large exceptions containing valuetypes</summary>
  <text>
  When an exception is sent, the message size is pre-calculated. If
  the message spanned multiple buffers, the current output pointer
  calculation was wrong, leading to incorrect marshalling of
  indirections.
  </text>
</bug>

<bug id="6" date="Thu May 23 12:54:55 BST 2013" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>Bidirectional GIOP fails in MAIN_THREAD_POLICY POAs</summary>
  <text>
  When an object reference that should have been subject to
  bidirectional GIOP was unmarshalled on a call destined for a main
  thread POA, it was not correctly marked for bidirectional.
  </text>
</bug>

<bug id="5" date="Thu May 23 12:04:39 BST 2013" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>Improper handling of transport rules containing names</summary>
  <text>
  If a transport rule contains a name, it is resolved to an IP
  address, but the rule was installed with the original name, rather
  than the resolved address.
  </text>
</bug>

<bug id="4" date="Wed Apr 10 18:13:58 BST 2013" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>omniNames service startup failure led to a crash</summary>
  <text>
  If the omniNames Windows service failed to start, it would crash
  rather than failing gracefully.
  </text>
</bug>

<bug id="3" date="Fri Dec 21 14:08:04 GMT 2012" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>Invalid generated code for valuetypes with no members</summary>
  <text>
  TypeCodes generated for valuetypes with no members were invalid.
  </text>
</bug>

<bug id="2" date="Thu Aug 23 15:43:07 BST 2012" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>Valuetype chunked encoding errors</summary>
  <text>
  The chunked encoding for valuetypes could sometimes be incorrect.
  </text>
</bug>

<bug id="1" date="Sat Mar 17 20:34:10 GMT 2012" user="dgrisby">
  <summary>Obtaining IP addresses could fail on Solaris</summary>
  <text>
  The Solaris lifconf structure was incorrectly initialised, meaning
  that the call to obtain IP addresses could fail.
  </text>
</bug>

</buglist>
